<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sustainability | Maulany Citra&#39;s portfolio</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/sustainability/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/sustainability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Sustainability</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu_6baa9bd8930efa46.png</url>
      <title>Sustainability</title>
      <link>https://example.com/tags/sustainability/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>🧠 New Volunteer for Baduy Program</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/volunteer---baduy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/volunteer---baduy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Citra has just signed up as a &lt;strong&gt;volunteer committee member for the Baduy Program&lt;/strong&gt;, in collaboration with &lt;strong&gt;Bakti Milenial&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Paragon&lt;/strong&gt;. Through this initiative, she will support environmental conservation efforts and the preservation of the indigenous Baduy culture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although still in the registration phase, this initiative offers the chance to be directly involved in projects aimed at promoting sustainability and preserving the cultural heritage of the Baduy community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;activities-to-be-conducted&#34;&gt;Activities to be Conducted&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Environmental Conservation&lt;/strong&gt;: Educating on the importance of sustainability and eco-friendly practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cultural Preservation&lt;/strong&gt;: Supporting and promoting the unique traditions of the Baduy people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;other-activities&#34;&gt;Other Activities&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, Citra is also engaged in several other initiatives, such as:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Merdeka Student Exchange Program&lt;/strong&gt;: Participating in a student exchange program that provides cultural insights from various regions in Indonesia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pemimpin.id Initiative&lt;/strong&gt;: Actively participating in leadership development projects aimed at empowering youth across Indonesia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Akhwat Poster Design Competition&lt;/strong&gt;: Competing in a design competition focused on social impact and inspiration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did you find this page helpful? Consider sharing it 🙌&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Completion of Generasi Bebas Plastik: A Collaborative Effort Towards Reducing Plastic Waste</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publication/generasi-bebas-plastik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/publication/generasi-bebas-plastik/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Generasi Bebas Plastik&lt;/strong&gt; initiative has been successfully completed, bringing together a community dedicated to reducing plastic waste. Over two weeks, participants engaged in activities like sorting and recycling waste, creating educational content, and visiting recycling facilities to gain deeper insights into sustainable practices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This program aimed to build better waste management habits, raise public awareness, and inspire collective action to tackle the global issue of plastic waste. Notable outcomes include a reduction in the use of single-use plastics and an increase in the adoption of reusable items such as bottles, bags, and food containers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Generasi Bebas Plastik&lt;/strong&gt; team remains committed to further promoting sustainable lifestyles and encouraging everyone to take small yet impactful actions in their daily lives. Together, we can make a difference in reducing environmental harm caused by plastic waste.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generasi Bebas Plastik</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/generasi-bebas-plastik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/generasi-bebas-plastik/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A community-driven project focused on reducing plastic waste by educating and engaging local communities. It involves workshops, awareness campaigns, and collaboration with local waste management systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
