<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog | Maulany Citra&#39;s portfolio</title>
    <link>https://example.com/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu_6baa9bd8930efa46.png</url>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>🎉 Managing Social Media at NovoClub</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/smm-novoclub/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/smm-novoclub/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a dedicated social media manager for &lt;strong&gt;NovoClub&lt;/strong&gt;, Citra is responsible for developing creative content, managing interactions, and amplifying the club&amp;rsquo;s online presence. Through strategic planning, she enhances the club’s engagement with its members and builds meaningful connections within the community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-responsibilities&#34;&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content Creation&lt;/strong&gt;: Curating and posting engaging content for Facebook, Instagram, and Twitter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Engagement&lt;/strong&gt;: Actively interacting with members and followers, ensuring a positive and inclusive atmosphere.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brand Partnerships&lt;/strong&gt;: Collaborating with like-minded organizations to expand the club’s reach and foster new opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;did-you-find-this-page-helpful-consider-sharing-it-&#34;&gt;Did you find this page helpful? Consider sharing it 🙌&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>👩🏼‍🏫 Empowering Future Leaders with Pemimpin.ID</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/pemimpin-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/pemimpin-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Citra is a passionate mentor within the &lt;strong&gt;Pemimpin.ID&lt;/strong&gt; community, where she actively supports young leaders through workshops, training sessions, and one-on-one guidance. Her work focuses on empowering individuals to lead with integrity, empathy, and vision, fostering a new generation of changemakers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;mentoring-highlights&#34;&gt;Mentoring Highlights&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leadership Training&lt;/strong&gt;: Conducting workshops on leadership skills, goal-setting, and effective communication.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One-on-one Guidance&lt;/strong&gt;: Providing personalized mentorship to young leaders, helping them identify and pursue their passions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Engagement&lt;/strong&gt;: Encouraging mentees to get involved in social causes and community-based projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;did-you-find-this-page-helpful-consider-sharing-it-&#34;&gt;Did you find this page helpful? Consider sharing it 🙌&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🧠 Designing for Change - Lomba Poster Akhwat</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/akhwat-poster-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/akhwat-poster-design/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Citra participated in the &lt;strong&gt;Lomba Design Poster Akhwat&lt;/strong&gt;, using her design skills to promote significant social causes, including the struggles faced by Palestinians. Through her artwork, she communicated powerful messages of solidarity and women’s empowerment, highlighting important global issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;design-focus&#34;&gt;Design Focus&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advocacy for Palestinian rights&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Promoting women’s empowerment through visual arts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributing to a greater sense of community and social justice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By participating in this contest, Citra&amp;rsquo;s work not only showcased her creative abilities but also conveyed her commitment to raising awareness about these pressing global causes. Through her designs, she aimed to inspire others to reflect on their role in addressing human rights and social justice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;did-you-find-this-page-helpful-consider-sharing-it-&#34;&gt;Did you find this page helpful? Consider sharing it 🙌&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🧠 New Volunteer for Baduy Program</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/volunteer---baduy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/volunteer---baduy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Citra has just signed up as a &lt;strong&gt;volunteer committee member for the Baduy Program&lt;/strong&gt;, in collaboration with &lt;strong&gt;Bakti Milenial&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Paragon&lt;/strong&gt;. Through this initiative, she will support environmental conservation efforts and the preservation of the indigenous Baduy culture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although still in the registration phase, this initiative offers the chance to be directly involved in projects aimed at promoting sustainability and preserving the cultural heritage of the Baduy community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;activities-to-be-conducted&#34;&gt;Activities to be Conducted&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Environmental Conservation&lt;/strong&gt;: Educating on the importance of sustainability and eco-friendly practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cultural Preservation&lt;/strong&gt;: Supporting and promoting the unique traditions of the Baduy people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;other-activities&#34;&gt;Other Activities&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, Citra is also engaged in several other initiatives, such as:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Merdeka Student Exchange Program&lt;/strong&gt;: Participating in a student exchange program that provides cultural insights from various regions in Indonesia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pemimpin.id Initiative&lt;/strong&gt;: Actively participating in leadership development projects aimed at empowering youth across Indonesia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Akhwat Poster Design Competition&lt;/strong&gt;: Competing in a design competition focused on social impact and inspiration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did you find this page helpful? Consider sharing it 🙌&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>📈 Broadening Horizons through the Student Exchange PMM</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/pmm-unram/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/pmm-unram/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Through the &lt;strong&gt;Merdeka Student Exchange Program&lt;/strong&gt;, Citra broadened her horizons while studying at &lt;strong&gt;Universitas Mataram&lt;/strong&gt;. This experience enhanced her leadership and intercultural communication skills, shaping her desire to contribute to education and community development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;program-outcomes&#34;&gt;Program Outcomes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engaged with diverse student groups to exchange ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participated in community service projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed a deeper understanding of cultural dynamics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;did-you-find-this-page-helpful-consider-sharing-it-&#34;&gt;Did you find this page helpful? Consider sharing it 🙌&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
