<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tahfidz | Maulany Citra&#39;s portfolio</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/tahfidz/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/tahfidz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Tahfidz</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu_6baa9bd8930efa46.png</url>
      <title>Tahfidz</title>
      <link>https://example.com/tags/tahfidz/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tahfidz - Regular Program - Arrasyid</title>
      <link>https://example.com/teaching/tahfidz---regular-program---arrasyid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/teaching/tahfidz---regular-program---arrasyid/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At &lt;strong&gt;Ar-Rasyid Learning Center&lt;/strong&gt;, we specialize in Quranic studies, focusing on &lt;strong&gt;Tahfidz&lt;/strong&gt; (memorization), &lt;strong&gt;Tahsin&lt;/strong&gt; (improvement of recitation), and &lt;strong&gt;Tajwid&lt;/strong&gt; (rules of proper pronunciation). Our program is designed to help students not only memorize the Quran but also develop an understanding of its correct recitation, following the Islamic rules of Tajwid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;learning-approach&#34;&gt;Learning Approach&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tahfidz&lt;/strong&gt;: We guide students through the process of memorizing the Quran, ensuring they can retain and recall its verses with confidence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tahsin&lt;/strong&gt;: Aiming to improve the fluency and beauty of Quranic recitation, focusing on correct pronunciation and articulation of words.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tajwid&lt;/strong&gt;: In-depth study of the rules of pronunciation, ensuring that every letter is pronounced correctly, adhering to the traditional rules of Tajwid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-features&#34;&gt;Key Features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personalized Learning&lt;/strong&gt;: Every student is given a personalized learning plan based on their memorization pace and recitation skill.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experienced Instructors&lt;/strong&gt;: Our instructors are dedicated to helping students perfect their recitation and achieve their memorization goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moral and Spiritual Growth&lt;/strong&gt;: Beyond academic learning, we focus on nurturing the moral and spiritual development of each student, fostering a deeper connection to the Quran.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-goal&#34;&gt;Our Goal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To help students achieve a strong connection with the Quran through memorization, accurate recitation, and the application of Tajwid, making Quranic studies an integral part of their daily lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;did-you-find-this-page-helpful-consider-sharing-it-&#34;&gt;Did you find this page helpful? Consider sharing it 🙌&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
