<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks | Maulany Citra&#39;s portfolio</title>
    <link>https://example.com/event/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu_6baa9bd8930efa46.png</url>
      <title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks</title>
      <link>https://example.com/event/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mapres Talks - Sharing Stories of Achievement and Growth</title>
      <link>https://example.com/event/maprestalks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/event/maprestalks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;flex px-4 py-3 mb-6 rounded-md bg-primary-100 dark:bg-primary-900&#34;&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;pr-3 pt-1 text-primary-600 dark:text-primary-300&#34;&gt;
  &lt;svg height=&#34;24&#34; xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 24 24&#34;&gt;&lt;path fill=&#34;none&#34; stroke=&#34;currentColor&#34; stroke-linecap=&#34;round&#34; stroke-linejoin=&#34;round&#34; stroke-width=&#34;1.5&#34; d=&#34;m11.25 11.25l.041-.02a.75.75 0 0 1 1.063.852l-.708 2.836a.75.75 0 0 0 1.063.853l.041-.021M21 12a9 9 0 1 1-18 0a9 9 0 0 1 18 0m-9-3.75h.008v.008H12z&#34;/&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&#34;dark:text-neutral-300&#34;&gt;Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;inspirational-stories-from-mapres-talks&#34;&gt;Inspirational Stories from Mapres Talks&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday, September 25, 2024, &lt;strong&gt;Mapres Talks&lt;/strong&gt; was held as part of the &lt;strong&gt;PKKMB X MASTA 2024&lt;/strong&gt; event at Campus 2 ITESA Muhammadiyah Semarang. This event featured outstanding students (Mapres) as speakers who shared their stories about academic challenges, organizational experiences, and the achievements they have attained.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;event-highlights&#34;&gt;Event Highlights&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Struggles on the Path to Success&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Outstanding students shared the biggest challenges they faced in achieving success. One of the speakers, a student who excelled academically and in community activities, shared how she managed her time and priorities despite the many challenges. They emphasized the importance of continuous growth and persistence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Message About the Importance of Consistency&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
One of the key takeaways came from another speaker, who stressed the importance of &lt;strong&gt;consistency&lt;/strong&gt; in achieving goals. They said:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Don’t be afraid to try. Start with small steps and keep doing it every day, because great achievements begin with the consistency of small actions.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Motivation and Hope for New Students&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
During the Q&amp;amp;A session, participants were eager to ask about overcoming procrastination and finding passion in their academic journey. The speakers emphasized that &lt;strong&gt;the process of self-discovery&lt;/strong&gt; is a vital part of the journey, and new students should be open to learning and exploring new interests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;inspiration-from-outstanding-students&#34;&gt;Inspiration from Outstanding Students&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Mapres Talks&lt;/strong&gt; event at &lt;strong&gt;PKKMB X MASTA 2024&lt;/strong&gt; was an inspiring session for new students. Outstanding students shared:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Academic achievements&lt;/strong&gt;, including awards, competitions, and their journey to becoming outstanding students.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizational experiences&lt;/strong&gt;, including their involvement in BEM, IMM, and external communities beyond campus, which provided them with significant benefits and shaped their leadership and teamwork skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Memorable moments&lt;/strong&gt;, such as participating in the &lt;strong&gt;Pertukaran Mahasiswa Merdeka (PMM)&lt;/strong&gt; program and competing in the &lt;strong&gt;ONMIPA Olympiad&lt;/strong&gt; outside their island, which offered them new insights, experiences, and opportunities to build broader networks by meeting many new people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With enthusiasm and passion, the speakers encouraged participants to dream big, overcome challenges, and seize opportunities to achieve success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;event-atmosphere&#34;&gt;Event Atmosphere&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The session was interactive, with many questions from the audience eager to learn more about the journeys of the Mapres speakers. The entire event was filled with positive energy and a spirit of togetherness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Participant Quote:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;It’s so inspiring! I now realize that success isn’t about speed, but about consistency and the process.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speaker’s Impression:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;It was a pleasure sharing my story and meeting eager students. I hope they are inspired to unleash their best potential.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;event-documentation&#34;&gt;Event Documentation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To view more highlights from Mapres Talks, visit:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Instagram: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/pkkmbxmasta.itesa&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;@pkkmbxmasta.itesa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Mapres Talks&lt;/strong&gt; event proved that sharing stories and experiences is a great way to spark new motivation. A big thank you to all the speakers, participants, and organizers who made this event a success! 🎉&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;event-overview&#34;&gt;Event Overview&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Mapres Talks: Sharing Stories of Achievement and Growth&lt;/strong&gt; is an exclusive session in the &lt;strong&gt;PKKMB X MASTA 2024&lt;/strong&gt; program, where outstanding students (Mapres) share their success stories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Key highlights of this session include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal journeys of growth and academic achievement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lessons learned from overcoming challenges.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motivational tips for balancing academics and extracurricular activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
